### Contact

egypt 01149948099 (Mobile) ahmedfathi520@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ahmedfathi-382441133 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Web Development

Design

Graphics

#### Certifications

Certificate of completion -Introduction to Data and Data Science

# Ahmed Fathi

data science enthusiast || civil engineer || future data scientist Giza

# Summary

Hello,

I Am Ahmed Fathi

Front End Developer

I Work In Front-End Web Development, And I Have Experience In Dealing With Programming And Modern Web Technologies, And I Have Built A Lot Of Projects That Have Increased My Experience And Trained A Lot, I Am A Fast Learner And Always Love To Develop Myself

# Experience

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) Student October 2021 - Present (3 months)

#### **PETROJET**

Trainee

June 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 3 months)

worked as a trainee civil engineer in somid project

## Education

technology

technical, Computer Systems Networking (2013 - 2015)

Ain Shams University

Bachelor's degree, Civil Engineering (2015 - 2020)

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

Higher National Diploma, web design · (2021 - 2021)